Ania duceria
but I think you read the announcement of this
egoist
and
psychotherapy Sărulești my
and evening Five years ago Who said that we will
teach you
something unusual for a book
looking to kill and the book said that a
Poem that I was enrolled 400 years ago
about
king and I this was written by the
Saints this first step of not fighting
Sankt Ciuc equal 10 cm and
I love him is an extraordinary teacher you
were here ba
[Music]
PSI I had 20 years ago taught for
three years at dai mounting between them
is a poet
[Music]
great extraordinary
wrote the secret poem I translated a lot of it
one of my students who I was not really that good
published it without
asking me what if it is
secret poetry and possibly you can you can find
somewhere
Who is an extraordinary poem about
his secret practice
Then he wrote extraordinary books of
philosophy and I heard
his explanation
about the fact that their work turns
into a living diamond if you are successful on
this path and not  I think you can find
this elsewhere
expressed and outlined clearly and
this
actually meant the transformation of the five parts
of the body and the mind and maybe one
day we will go through this together
he also wrote on a
famous clarion call
which means
my way to
ecstasy or which easy to ecstasy and
I started
pste Find the
part of the
advanced courses and I and time I set out
to teach these courses
But as many people and we talked
about this and now I thought
today that we could just go through the
poem
I started reading this Poem 11
years ago and I started translating it
I had a program in Phoenix In Arizona
the second we have So let's in in
and I remain a scare Scarborought there
is like a public garden and in
Arizona we don't really have psychic rain
[Music]
that garden is quite brief but it was
very wonderful and I
started this
teaching 11 years ago
What do you do I undress and when
my teacher taught and taught me
this
book I
hear the microphones of
several children  Well in the microphone
more more children and this is a
microphone there yes related to the book is that
I never finished
and
he died too so
I tried to
finish
translating because It's extraordinary
and Let me tell you some ideas about
this
vertigo dizziness The Angel in this step case
is actually the understanding of the pen
but in this book in his poetry
and I
think we are
a beautiful being wise milk What
is that part of our mind
but I don't know how it is in your country but in the
country where I live
and this pictures at Black Tisa
special as you saw in your mind the image at the
beginning of the announcement of other
images an image with an angel standing
on one side and the devil standing on the
other side and around me
always trying To make me
eat donuts the angel
vegetables and all the time to fight throughout
a day and I don't know when I
think it's
the devil says it wouldn't be good for me to
eat a donut man
and Yes I understand that they are not that good for
you we more but you know it's one of those things in
life
if  you eat a like that every now and then it's
okay
and then the Baltic Angel not everything you
eat becomes part of you and what you
eat
and every time you eat something
unhealthy becomes part of your body
Yesterday I had
[Music]
a very interesting teaching
is that you eat day what you eat That's what we
say in English because
what you eat your body becomes
transforms so actually
today my body
no less now support for my wife
psbo Because of this weekend We both have
a sick man from the children this week
I mother recovered me first take still a
little sick so I rinse it for her so
the devil is trying to finish you
eat a donut and the Angel I'm going to say
no no no don't eat some vegetables and then it's going to
start arguing inside
your mind
psychologist actually in this extremely interested man
just that the Angel specifically is
actually my understanding of the text
understanding
Ok So ready when I hand over the pen
From what to get into so much perdum and
want  than to tell you really I don't know but do
n't understand yes it's another side fire
Moldova of the true and if everyone
in the world would be logical if we were
fully not logical
do after I explain the pen eggs
but every time and in this
biscuits
[Music]
psychiatrist have this O lost That I see a
little Yes and every time Arad I show them to
a dog he wants to gnaw they didn't
see na x stay their and it seems like a
story about for children Yes it's like a
story that you tell
children
before bed maybe the first
could write a short story to you It sounds
like a children's story but it's not and it's
one hundred percent true if your mind is
truly pure and clean list
poster see it understand it is already proven
could percent that things from us
and do not come from I understand them and I know that it
sounds to you So simple
I read it a thousand times
maybe you are of bored to
hear about x but if you really
understand
that only in this way will you be able to change
this name
I say we have this word in Buddhism called
command ala
and  That means an image of a
perfect world and where there is no disease no death
no anger and all you care about Okay And
if the wooden pen the story about is
true then Mandala Is possible
then it is possible to change and
change this world
and maybe you have heard of places like a
paradise lamaite Well I'm without this
heat Vision and so right and there really is
this free place and I've heard
sometimes a some people I say to it wouldn't
be so boring Let's
see Always the same thing but not us
more fun But
who other people I prepare that
psychotechnics babes
pshs60 I even heard
people who explained What does the
origin of addiction mean
only because of the
bad things we can see the good things and
that is completely wrong
and I think a tray silly and we can't
say you went only if you have something
else and it's not true put Yes And you can still
go even if you don't have a banana
Yes it is possible
if the pen comes from me
then I can make a perfect world and we
should do that places like
paradise lamaite Well yes
this guy from there already  they finished they've been on
this line for a long time And
by the way
we have the same lesson and we're
basically the same and all these Buddhas and
all the passive enlightened being started so
we and they're not different from us
at first I always thought that
grapes
if we're like the students in the back of
the class the most demanding and the students in the
front of the house always raise their hand and
say I know I know what That's nice die
but how and commerce and art
third I'm going back These guys already have
absorption
We're like the students in the back of the
class But there's nothing here we're catching up
and what And these types of
teachings will teach us will help us to
this norm and in the shower and with me
We'll live introduce perfectly and I've seen
this world and you can teach other
people and be funny fun to do
this together yes it's great
and I like this format about
angels and they have who speaks in the mind and the
devil who speaks in the other
side because during a day
you and I are the same yes in we have
on trial speaks reports and
the devil elsewhere all
day long
in the ancient books of abidal it is
said that it is possible to read
other people's minds if I meditate well and you can
learn to do this in person If the wound
flows well Yes so you can do a like
for this from West side and so
I can learn to read you can read
other people's minds but it's not funny you
think maybe you have the feeling that it's funny
but it's not really sad that all these
arguments in someone's mind
this
crowding me on thoughts from the mind of a
member of a person and if you really
could read someone's mind it wouldn't be
very funny because we all have an
angel and a man who is arguing and
arguing all day and let's
start
this matter is when I teach
about this
and I think we have
three more sessions so we will less we have
in the next two years
three more sessions and we should be able to
read this together And we finish it and
then we will publish it at Deichmann in the
book rare
venerable ut pas to what the whole team
there
and I think we have  need a comment
because it's a difficult book I forgot
to tell you one more thing about the
author
that I like the most about
bison is that he's been there while
for a retreat between a cave and a
and that if I've ever done
long retreats you know those
people else menu cook for
you and you can't go out and buy and
cook so he had
a
[Music]
a guy who bought him food and I
forgot that person left him a
swim Write something on a piece of paper and they
usually tried not to want to not
talk
instead left him something written and said
bad news you have to move next door
until he finishes everything
else and patient to me asked why
be the
people from eMAG at the store I know what's going to
be a war that's
going to start tomorrow
when you sleep who will come to this
area two Generals are just leading mate and
a fight is going to start and a lot of
people are going to die helium and
Smart have to me and here stay here
in  this ice cave here took
blood and then they think they guessed and
Can you imagine II
Don't beat me at mom was the same as us Yes
said late have it's pretty scary I should
go
[Music]
pack my things
and everything I have here until By meditate what
should I leave to go next to another mount
and I think we feel like it But thought and I
did the same
and then he couldn't sleep it kept
growing and more and more
Wow if people were fighting tomorrow I'm going back
Vali a lot of people are going to
die
And it's not a good thing I should do
something for this
what I like that
morning at and from shooting are Robert
shooting and writing man
building something here people who came are
bringing food and I'm
a pretty famous lamei so He
said
Tomorrow I have later in the day bring the ball bring some
gold coins
two two leave with gold and Let's try
to stop this war and when
those just me They have to gather to
fight he came out of the cave and on the
field  of battle
and I'm standing between the two armies and he
was already a famous teacher of sorts
simple said do if you want to kill each other I
should rest on
me first and I don't have much
here both armies were confused and
both respected him and he tells the
two Generals to come here and have a
conversation so the two Generals
came to the battlefield and
he says 10 let's sit down and
talk
[Music]
Psalm suggestion related to this war
and those generalizing Ok Which is
suggestive it says when I put on me
quite famous
people offer
org.com here and two bags you with
gold coins and my suggestion is that
offer this bag to this general
And offer this bag to the other
general why don't you want to go
home and relax and don't
especially I'll be
and then in the two kids
the two generals were very happy
give take one the ones with gold and sit take
home and they lived  happy
but also very simple How can I solve
the War and I like the girl for a long time she
was so brave so wise
system an extraordinary thinker so
now I'm going to read everything I want to
say you said let's read the peaks I don't know
how far we're going to get Grandpa
always tells stories and doesn't go
too fast
and we're going to try to have this one
shorter and have
question and answer sessions but there will be two
sessions this morning according to the
course uglier
pilots be careful that what happened so
in a few minutes we're going to take
in the trunk and mind we're going to take it
questions magic and I hope I take yes Then we're going to
finish Veronica's soup a e we're going to
start the next ones pull And by the way I
used these
teachings to
catch all my friends in the area to
donate Arizona to join
Shift burns Na and very amu me beautiful
when we all gather for the teachings in at the
colleague in Sedona
and I think I'm still contagious
believe
that I had
last week I have a but even so I don't want
to
know  count down and give to others
and in these two days I'm going to stay home
to feel sorry for this
it's better to be safe and even so
together and Come on somtum let's
start
my mom good eco met Oops I'm still hanging around
Come here I dance Coco
that
's ok E you're looking for it in pieces and I mean we take it
in pieces exactly in Buddhism they say that
when you die if you were
really to pink us
with your money and if you offered What is the
first perfection
some people would say quality I'm going to
offer
Na I would put
sharing if you want to share
that you offer
your time money and wisdom with
other people after you die
See You have to give birth like somewhere around me lies
like Dedeman or na
is the dose when you see when you
see him on the air in Man super mind
are 4 Fantastic
or talking to you but all these heroes
look like cows and I think this
these companies were
made by people who remember
their previous lives and I think
the people who did this test
movies remember a clear  pretty
well go to the interiors and plant
seeds so extraordinary we share
what you already know with other people so that
after we die we can that we
go to this temporary paradise
of course we can Let's think it's a little
dangerous if these beings are also going to
die for a while and they're going to consume their
Good Karma So it's not the best place to
go
psalms Sure slushies neither when
he sees what the movies and
we can meet somewhere directly
in the year we have to
watch a movie on Netflix but
we can also meet them in real life
if They really exist
and if you could stay meet
you feel like you have their power is
like the most powerful dream they
have to fly stay or fight
bad people
this comes so much power theirs come from
it but like the pen
psyche for the whole ice And for
countless other previous lives By the way
If you listen to me Now if you excuse me
now if you are if you are sons it's clear
that you had Get previous Yes come on if
something happened once Surely because
twice care and now
computers will train works all the
time perfect and if if
the car doesn't work you have to
prepare them but it doesn't get better
even
if it still Nile your car make
strange orders or computers or
phone make strange noises like For
example
fix this now because if a
problem happens once it
can happen like that a second time or
thousands pfai that I don't know clearly and if you can be live be
alive now and
you can in fitness in fitness with strange
come on yes it's like you said no no don't be
supi Yes
but that the car is causing you
problems Monday I definitely
can change it and Tuesday
Wednesday
Theseus and if so if it happens
twice on the networks then it can
happen a billion euros just
because time is born [ __ ]
men with so when we see when we
read this probiotic stories from
a and we hear this stories from a
teacher in which we believe
what is they were special teacher and they
shared with us everything he had and
then died this these seeds created the realms
of you are like Superheroes
Touch but then  says swear
If this
Deva is
if of will comes from Diva so Complex
comes from the pen How can you die
And how could they end their
diva lives and how can they go to other places
So if this pen exam And you have it
comes from himself Xbox That he could not run out of
ink Yes so if the pen comes from
him in should run out of
ink.me not possible so if a
person
comes from himself to the two is already
so should na but he has to die
but and could not change this we
say heaven Yes as
I like today's lesson and
tomorrow because sometimes the Angel doesn't really
talk much I think a little shy
and maybe a lot of angels are like that
Speed ​​objective so the Angel doesn't really
talk that much and in this
section here it says
if a little comes from a pen
and if the person comes from himself
How could he die
and he says posí to means How could he
die and PSI take to another realm
and this is the poem that  we're going to
talk today and tomorrow and then we're going to
talk about how it happens and what
happens when we die what happens what happens
to us at that moment is
a very strange thing
perfect on i go to
princeton university and one of the greatest
universities and i think that of the world
and we spent
four five years there and nobody is
any one course no lesson there on
how to die and very funny yes
in the whole university
god specialists say that doing our
staff
vila8 meow wonderful dollars that they
run and but there is no Lesson
on how to teach you How about how
or how to die
it's like you have buildings the whole
universe but without a bathroom like you have
late war you would have to go to the
toilet and a little thin to
me to build the university of the
sea and not have a bathroom hey so i can
be
about two or three hours from you you
need a bathroom so a I don't
know and i remember in
japan where then
but if you ever think of building a
university put a
in the air bathroom there and if you teach
people  about life you learn about
death but otherwise not it this is not
a complete university and here in heaven
say if you came from yourself
how could you die And then what
happens to Maybe when you go to
go to the next life what
happens What should we ask ourselves
this question but we have to care about this I
care about this if someone says
was the luggage quickly Yes And where am I
going I don't know don't worry about going for
something
but and when you go in the next How much
money but don't worry loan
pack like this and be prepared And
if you don't ask where you're going and do
n't ask where should I go and
Why do you have to pack Yes you're crazy
this life is short feel
Yesterday I was at had 25 years now I'm
my hair is a little red now and that this happens to
anyone and we should prepare but
not stay here forever
someone should take care of this so
what can they do at this time what Let's
go to verse 242
charma more  we see
Gheorghe neamțiu gama and then the devil
says to the bathroom hey ready Yes everyone Ok
but everyone goes somewhere where they
go from where after they die because you
came from somewhere here Yes don't be stupid not to
When I die I will disappear Well no you
are not here So Let's go but he didn't
understand that after death You will go somewhere else
Yes you came here Where do I go
and if something happened once it will
happen twice and maybe he understands
this
everyone should fix their
car if it were otherwise as he
says but no they don't people die
life continues to and then the Angel you say
No you didn't say that the dream exists by itself so I ca
n't die if the pen
exists from Huawei from who up I
know including you can exist from
yourself if you exist so you can't
change What is a reason why you
change this has a difficult idea
if the pen comes from itself as
we believe new laws
mean when it should change and should
n't stay  without ink and
if the ink is in the pen it should not
run out of ink in the house and it does not
die I am to that here already at I just
said if the dream comes from the
factory people made from oil but not from
mom buy from the store curtains
unspoken that you come man cannot change of
course it changes this time we have to go
to the store to buy another
one
but the mistake says Come on be careful if
the pen comes from the store
if the pen was made in the factory
then it cannot change
and it should not run out of ink
down to unspoken never That
of course the dream is made in the top
for a factory
if you write things to me the ink is and you
write on paper air and it runs out of
ink and after that you have to buy
another one and I never said the pen does
not change
but you think about it because
we asked where
the pen really comes from don't ask that Do
n't ask that Why did the Psalm come to
me is
this is a very very important thing
if you want to have a happy life
and a successful death is a
strange word I don't know if you want to have a
happy life and a successful death you have to
ask yourself where you came from
not how you came into this world
but why you came into this world
and if you tell me why the
pen came arrived at the store then
Gisela was made in Japan Yes
They Yes the factory
took the Oil and they made it cool from there
Well boredom
and I say No you tell me
what was how the pen came to me and you do
n't tell me why would choose
what you should try to understand the
difference not the pen how the pen came To
me they
give them made between a factory and but they
transported all the way to America and then you
bought I don't understand I understand me
how it came to me But why to me and
why this pic to me Be careful with e I
do nothing outside every day and
some questions didn't answer funny and
yes you lost the password it's at the fair
I want too much
in the corner bye bye this question
so this pic came to me don't
worry use it Yes yes christof I
tell you you are
smart you should  you wonder
why your car broke down today why it
makes strange sounds get rid of why it makes
strange sounds Why does the computer on the
behave strangely And not quite yes I know that
when
I start the car after a few thousand they make
strange sounds This but The question is
Why my car
only Hello time don't jump broken
my car not Stalin's broke nor
sage's car this broken So my car so
if you are an
eby person wait here intelligent you have to
ask yourself why me why not how that I
short on Yes my module broke or like the
next something happened distance and that's why
you take out with the sounds but don't
say How do we say Why Why does my car
have these sounds from the carburetor and not
his car time and not Sebi's car
come on sad in the back a question
what's important is more important I don't know
what else you have planned are you still doing
today I have to get to my colleagues
to get something else finish the
soup for my wife and things like that
Yes and you think in you have an
advance with mouse that with us what to do
during the day but the day you do
a  journey to die from this the other
side because this will happen I'm
sure I don't know if
if I get to Arad
this psychology or if the upset will
burn but I know for sure that it's possible to die
and it should be I'm preparing for
this We should ask ourselves Why do we
die and not with dying
and that's what we'll do
in the next lesson by a journalist
I hope we'll do a 15 minute trapeze Yes I'm
going early we still have that Look it's
a bit is an OK Stone
is an already established program Yes I
have Ok Gheorghe dinica and before why
we'll have the voltage of short
questions and answers Come on
feel
psychomotor like we give
life That I can say
psychologists many them without without hair
likes to me because you can stand like that so it does
n't look good and the first lesson me
question ice
we know that look everything comes from us and
applies to everyone even children and how
can we think
[Music]
such as for example
to the victims
Gheorghe hânsă domestic violence and
those people who suffer so much and
another question  extraordinary
Bologna yes you know I have
between Athens Mongolian monastery 25 years
and I
pfai were Buddhists and there were about 50
Mongolian monks Mongolian monk and I
lived there 25 years alcohol my teacher
in Romanian what near nuiorg
and I learned to catch a and I did
after
install I was accepted to a college
and I was very active in within the
church and allegedly had an extraordinary cathedral
similar to Notre Dame in Paris I think they
stole their plans very beautiful
and the music was beautiful it was a
quiet place wonderful and very
expensive maybe millions of dollars I don't know
you
airwaves Yes and from bringstone went
straight to this small lung Gold
Ciao
wonderful statues there of Buddha
Maitreya
[Music]
but Also there are
terrible paintings but on Turcu hells the
music was incredible boom boom boom
thin and I think we couldn't go
all the members opinions that it sounds to me like I have
World War II and I said to
try
How
can you have these paintings on the walls
and the music is very loud and  you can
meditate says every culture has its
own custom in Mongolia is
like a church Wonderful and This is
their tradition be different from the custom
in princeton but different and
okay
Scholl Find
feel for a It was another role of the
teacher were in part that
circulate a
Nazi [ __ ] Yes So
[Music]
who practiced killed millions of people
Yes And it was this struggle like but actually
this sign comes from ancient India Gigi we figure it out
exactly Teo
[Music]
pfai two thousand years before
Hitler and the Nazis
and mine explained everything we will forgive and we
were ok do this maybe Hitler
took this meaning to used
end maybe at a delay when
Jews but gets to that temple and would
see the chair and say a
beautiful lady and a problem this and it was was
my job because I was actually the
guy who does the
tour but and
I go with them and practically everything
and before my teacher comes I say you know
what
Come on when this will be like Yes we
take it out until a  under the chair and didn't show and I
asked Why and he said he wouldn't
understand
possibly to think that we are given
and that we are bad and just
hide but it's not a show
what I said no no it's not okay can you
explain those it's really no no it's not too
early to explain this to people I
'm not ready
Yes They've seen this symbol their whole
life and even if they listened they wouldn't
understand this feel comfortable in
our temple
I want you to hide but and I hid and we
had a nice time and everyone I was
happy and they laughed
and in the end abuse back to this was that
danger And why do I say this
in Buddhism adapter thought we go on a time
a time when the student is not ready
and I stay a time when we shouldn't
talk about certain things if
the student is not ready and I think
So come on children die in
car accidents and are in fires Yes what
little children why so many people
sexually abuse their children or other
types of abuse physical abuse
beatings why Why is it
happening What is the
reason is open the irbis and yes  should have
more of a reason and everything has a
cause there is nothing in this Universe
that does not have a cause anything has a search
anything has Well so what and not just a field
and not say how that child was abused
and with yes or taken to a certain place and
someone caught being abused this is as well
and you tell me how they were we
say Why Why This child and why don't you
have a child air
and in Buddhism
we have me where the answer to these
questions that's why we are all here
listening to this lesson Today to feel we feel
that we can really find the
right answers but it is
a time when people are not
ready for the answer verb and a time when we should just simply
show them compassion and love
and show them me a personal connection
and even Buddha did not answer directly
If he thought the student was not ready
and Yes is a reason
why children die in
car accidents at two years old fire and
are reason why
children some children are
abused and others not understand that they are
motivated but
ring like that most of the time in
our tradition and Gheorghe  Hagi mari
teacher say yes maybe the students I
'm not ready to hear this
maybe all they need is a
share or maybe they're sleeping with love and you
can explain it to them later when they
understand more you can explain to them about the
internal services about the seeds you
can explain to us that everything has a
cause but you have to
choose is the right time and when the
parents suffer it's not the right time
you have to hide festigal Yes it
's time to give them free even if it's just you
make them some balls and I beer and
make them feel better but I
understand that everything has a reason and has a
cause let's
go to which must be we must be
mine I met a even four
urgent and physical what children have problems
in the mother's womb I me I'm ready a pizza too much too
much sardine sauce
PSI the
unhappy child because he didn't
understand that that must be a time
before them yes and used to say
funny thing to This child his
whole life his mind was so
crazy because I ate pizza when she
was
pregnant I know what she combined with the wrong sauce but
of course not  there's no
point in going like and I think Buddha
always checked the student before we
need to
know my teacher I think he was a
Buddha and he taught me he's hiding it's going to be bad
if I don't have to tell you everything
from day one
and help you get to
his level and then later you
can teach him Why everything has a cause
Ok time do you have another gas question at the
beginning nobody told a
beautiful story about peace in my family that stopped
a war and some questions
that came up about
a potential war
this is the inspirational story and
that are simple so that we can
reduce and not experience
War is a tremendous question
go When
Yes You know the story I was a student at
Presto during high school during the
Vietnam War
and I was very disturbed by the laughter you
Golden Arghezi and I fought against the
war and I even went to
jail for a short time for
trying to stick
Me and my friends We tried to
shut down a weapons factory
when I was at Princeton and we did
[Music] we did
n't sit in front of the door and we didn't let
workers stay in and
produce Bond and the police came to take and
in we took them
arrested what we went to a
student meeting and all We were trying to stop the
war of we hear tight and there were thousands of
students this appointment and someone said
Let's drink we have the University
Yes the
study of the president care I hope we will
show them that we can stop this but
then I went I was shocked and I raised my
hand and I said eurokey.ro thousands of
students are no jokes to choose
exactly it
seems you are doing practice we do the same
thing But if it is bombing Vietnam what do I
do and to fix this You want to
bomb the school day
headquarters and it seems the same to me but
and I was disturbed by this and
then later I felt nothing but
discouraged I said sources
to work for several years
constantly to stop the war but it did not
help much and I felt that I
was the only person can not do
much
we were tens of trillions of
Vietnam and I do not know how I can stop the
War and now I am discouraged after that
in I did too many things
after  that incident and then I
studied something whose father with a my teacher
what I studied how to
open your seeds and where are they yes in
my environment as
my environment my moon comes from me just like the
pen Yes the world Where there is
conflict and there can be
serious conflicts alive and all of this comes from
me and now when I listen to
the news I'm on the news
when I was driving home from classes and you
should think this comes from
me this problem gets from me
and because it comes from me that I can get to
stop Yes so it's not the
given help to the neighbor if the pen
is right
you are never helpless You always
have a helper and anyone in the world
can help to stop this
conflict all We
can all do this brought to
but I'm only one to are thousands and
thousands of miles What can I do
but all the pen is these tensions both
very very serious situations
for everyone for the whole world the
blue team
time from us from each of us
each of us planted these
seeds for this conflicts this
tension and we see in our world
because  comes from us and because it
comes from me
a person Yes I can do something I don't have to give up my
tits to bomb the school I'm going to
go to jail Yes I can help
this situation as it is subject and very very
simple
we see people who no longer talk to each
other
actually I'm a little selfish and each side
no longer thinks about the other side of
Dacia want what they need
stay debts to the fact that I I planted
this thinning all day
I take care of myself
and I don't take care of other people and I'm so much
to be millions of people
ready who don't have in which today millions
and I have too much food Yes so
they
dry stop asked in war can I do
something if I can simply stop in
small seeds in means maybe I have a
some quarrels with someone my life or
maybe there's someone
in my life
exchange threatened by me and I don't want to
offend other people but maybe there are
certain people who need
my love I need my attention
I need me
to comfort you somehow and if they want I
could  I get to stay a lot I
connect with the people who need
me in my life Especially to
people who feel threatened by
me
then you can cancel But what do you feel
that I see flows so that's how the
people in this meeting
have the power to stop something you can do
something because they come from from you from
your seeds and very
and very
much Yes today you can
call someone
or to
or someone who has
felt any threatened by you and try
try to connect with the gods and
cancel the tension and then it changes and
that We'll go back to the text we'll see to keep me
next it can happen Yes
And I will be able to fix in
this life Na hou knew that you can change the
whole world world
then it's very easy to change
a little
crooked guesthouse grandpa has to go
check the soup and we'll take a 15
minute break and get back to our sheep